#### SENIOR PRODUCT MANAGER

Experience

senior product manager

March 2017 to Current Nice Systems il/4 Hoboken, NJ

- Own and manage quantitative real estate investment BI portal for the generation, grading and distribution of real estate leads.
- Use pattern recognition algorithms and machine learning to predict the probability of a homeowner to default on his mortgage.
- Analyze and interpret signals to generate real-time alerts & indicators using municipal, public and private big data.
- Work directly with CTO, project manager, system engineers, program managers, developers, testers and data scientists, utilizing best
  practices to define features and technical user stories Lead agile SDLC process, working in conjunction with end users, stakeholders and
  technical team.
- Acting as the main stakeholder of specific product backlog items, work closely with development teams to ensure the output to be aligned
  with acceptance criteria Being the voice of the client, assist in customer strategic RFX and providing a business perspective on value during
  day-to-day development Define the week-to-week tactical objectives to agile team, and provide quick JIT decisions to system level
  questions and defect triage Drive and own backlog grooming and management for future consideration and refinement.
- Stories prioritization, iterations within the agile team, drive acceptance testing and delivery of iteration.
- Conduct daily standup meetings, weekly refinements and demos meetings and management meeting in two weeks scrum sprints Oversee &
  direct data scientist, evaluate the research, approve the use of the data sources, API integrations Work directly with end users to capture
  and analyze challenges to their workflow, write detailed requirements, spec.
- · sheets and flow charts.

### June 2010 to April 2017 Bickford Senior Living il/4 Middletown, OH

- lead the team's vision, strategy and execution to deliver business results.
- Define the roadmap and own the proprietary web application for generating, scoring and distribution of sales leads.
- Collaborate with cross-functional team (designers, developers) to conceive, build, ship, and enhance features and products Work with
  program management stakeholders to support new business and maximize the work of the development team, introducing new strategic
  partners requiring new features of the platform
- Manage and lead Agile team of 6, backend/frontend engineers, UI designer and Dev-Ops Worked effectively to combine the vision of the
  product UI with in-house wireframe designers to provide clear design specifications Provided daily communications, notes, sprint reviews
  reports, project retrospectives, and regular snapshots of project velocity and budget burn rate Provide constant, rapid validation and
  iterative development.
- Work with 3rd party system integrators, data providers (data sources) to drive process on schedule and on budget.

# Digital marketing director

January 2005 to May 2010 Aramark Corp. i1/4 Prosper, TX

- Defined global vision and strategy in support of business, marketing and technology goals Orchestrate the planning and development of
  complex digital marketing and advertising plans Manage all aspects of digital media buys, and maintain marketing campaign initiatives by
  assuring deadlines are met, overseeing product development, and directing the design team Provided influential leadership to sales and
  marketing associates, providing customer service and technical training to create a strong workplace culture dedicated to the strategic
  planning objectives.
- Build optimize and test web forms, landing pages and templates of inbound lead generation campaigns.
- Initiate, negotiate and implement strategic partnerships to increase revenue from shared lead distribution platform like ping trees, implementing web API's Increased project revenues by as much as 50% due to mastery of SEO white hat tactics.
- Directed all digital marketing and web/mobile development activities improving project timelines and quality by 50% between IT and Marketing.
- leveraged mobile app store optimization (ASO) to drive app downloads by appearing at the top of search lists Led new customer
  acquisition campaigns through SEM, retargeting, & Facebook advertising Boosted revenue through paid advertising by 30% leveraging
  detailed analysis using Google Analytics and evaluation data with lead generation and innovative metrics tracking tools to make key
  decisions.

## Accomplishments

- Quantitative, predictive real estate investment portal involving AI & big data for the creation, management and distribution of graded property sales leads Cuff.co On Demand Self Storage mobile apps 'Uber' for self-storage, a simple, on-demand marketplace platform enabling users to earn income renting out storage and parking space in their homes as hosts, and let renters store their household items or rent a parking place for up to 50% cheaper than traditional self-storage.
- http://cuft.co/ https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/cuff/id1131641063 https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com/wepop.ondemand
   MovingCompanies.co Web and mobile apps that generates instant price quotes for moving services comparison.
- https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/moving-companies/id1081905208?mt=8 https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?
   id=com.moving.companies.movingcompanies http://www.movingcompanies.co HomeBulletin.net Proprietary lead distribution platform & a directory site with information and listings of moving & relocation related services 2.

#### Education

BA: Business Administration Marketing Finance Business Administration Marketing Finance military service, Israeli defence forces Infantry - Certification & Operational Activity Central Command Classified Function - Events &

## Operational Activity

Summary

Technology professional, entrepreneur and curious product guy with over 17 years of experience in management and ownership of business and consumer internet applications. Industry expertise in digital marketing, lead generation and business development. Built a successful company from the ground up, created, owned and brought to market web & mobile applications. Highlights

Jira, Confluence, Agile, Scrum, Kanban, Adobe Creative Cloud, Dreamweaver, Fireworx, Salesforce, Saas, Google Analytics, Google Search Console, Invision Studio, HTML, CSS, Google Developer Console, Apple Developer, Microsoft Office Suite, MySql. Skills

Adobe, Dreamweaver, advertising, Agile, API, Apple, big data, budget, BI, business management, business processes, charts, CSS, client, customer service, delivery, directing, fast, features, forms, functional, Google Analytics, HTML, leadership, logic, notes, machine learning, marketing, meetings, Microsoft Office Suite, MySql, optimization, Developer, organization skills, predict, product development, program management, quality, quick, Fast learner, real estate, real-time, research, sales, Scrum, SDLC, defence, self-motivated, Stories, strategy, strategic, strategic planning, technical training, triage, validation, verbal communication skills, vision, workflow, Excellent written